https://www.imcos.org/about-us/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Advertise on our site
IntroductionWe are committed to protecting the privacy of our members and supporters and treat all information you give us with great care.We promise to respect any personal details you share with us.  We aim to be clear when we collect your data and not to do anything you would not reasonably expect.Whenever you see the words we, our or us, it means the International Map Collectors’ Society (“IMCoS”).Where we collect information fromWe collect information when you give it to us directly or when it is publicly available.What personal data we collectWe collect your name, your contact details (postal and email), your collection interests (if you share them with us) and subscription details.  We do not hold any PayPal Account details or any credit card details; these items are processed on webpages operated by PayPal and Stripe respectively, and they do not pass any data back to us other than the amounts that have been paid.How we use your personal dataWe will mainly use your data:to provide you with information about the Society and other map-related matters which may be of relevant interest;to administer your subscriptions, and to send you the Quarterly Journal;to ensure that we know how you may be contacted.  It helps us to have a choice of how to contact you in case one method fails.We will not sell your personal details to third parties or share your details with others unless required to do so by law.How we keep your data safe and who has accessWe ensure that there are appropriate technical controls in place to protect your personal details.We will undertake regular reviews of who has access to the information that we hold to ensure that the information is only accessible by appropriate officers or members.We will make sure that any who carry out work on our behalf meet the same high standards that we adhere to when handling your personal information.Keeping your information up to datePlease do let us know if your details have changed.Your right to know what we know about you, make changes or to ask us to stop using your dataYou have a right to ask us to stop processing your personal data and if it is not necessary for the purpose you provided it to us we will do so.If you do not wish to hear from us that is fine.  Just let us know if you wish contact to cease.You have a right to a copy of the information we hold about you but please be aware that the Data Protection team may ask you for proof of identity in order to respond.You are entitled to have personal data rectified if inaccurate or incomplete.Changes to this policyWe may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  If we make any significant changes in the way we treat your personal information we will make this clear on the IMCoS website www.imcos.org or by contacting you directly.ContactIf you have any questions, comments or suggestions, please let us know by contacting IMCoS, via email to financialsecretary@imcos.org or by postal mail to Peter Walker, 10 Beck Road, Saffron Walden, Essex  CB11 4EH, UK.28 March 2018Log In
Username or Email Address
Password
Remember Me
CategoriesHistoryContactNational RepresentativesCollectingAwardsConstitution
All content and images © 2018 International Map Collectors' Society.
Website Design by Popcorn
MenuNewsEventsPast EventsJournalJournalsAdvertise with usAuthor guidelinesAbout UsCouncil & committeeContactCollectingAwardsHistoryPrivacy StatementGalleryJoinMember Login
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
